http://www.powerarchiver.com/privacy/

Products
WindowsPowerArchiver 2021 StandardPowerArchiver 2021 ProfessionalPowerArchiver 2021 ToolboxPowerArchiver 2021 For GovernmentPowerArchiver Enterprise UnlimitedPowerArchiver Educational UnlimitedPowerArchiver For Microsoft OfficePowerArchiver Command LineEncryption Suite Pro 2019MacOSPowerArchiver 2021 Pro for macOS
Support Support Form
Order Recovery
Forums
Company About Us
Awards
Contact Us
Resellers
Community News
PowerArchiver – Privacy Policy
We at ConeXware, Inc. are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) you share with us.
ConeXware, Inc. has established this Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information.
Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit ConeXware, Inc.’s Web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself.
ConeXware, Inc. strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, ConeXware, Inc. intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this Privacy Policy. Our goal is to provide protection for your Personal Information no matter where that Personal Information is collected, transferred, or retained.
Data Collection
ConeXware, Inc. collects Personal Information when you place an order for one of our products, request support from ConeXware, Inc., sign up for a newsletter, or submit a PowerArchiver skin.
When you place an order for one of our products, ConeXware, Inc. collects Personal Information as required to complete your order. This data includes your name, address, phone number, IP address and credit card details, depending on the payment method selected.
ConeXware, Inc. sometimes collects limited non-personally identifying information your browser makes available whenever you visit a Web site. This log information includes your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your query and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. We use this information to operate, develop and improve our services.
When we require personally identifying information, we will inform you about the types of information we collect and how we use it. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing your Personal Information with us.
Data Usage
Personal Information is strictly used for processing orders, or to contact you regarding a support request and newsletter update. Personal Information is not used for any other purposes.
The ConeXware, Inc. support staff uses the reliable LiveAgent support ticketing system for your support questions. Sending a support request requires no further information than your name and email address which are used solely for contact purposes in regards to your support request. Your data is relayed by LiveAgent and You can find out more about LiveAgent’s data protection and privacy policy here:
https://www.liveagent.com/gdpr/
Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
When you place an order for PowerArchiver or other ConeXware, Inc. products, our Web page utilizes “cookies” to uniquely identify your browser. A “cookie” is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. ConeXware, Inc. uses cookies only to correctly identify you throughout the order process.
You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will not be able to place an order for a ConeXware, Inc. product on our Web site.
Information Sharing
We do not rent or sell your personally identifying information to other companies or individuals, unless we have your consent. We may share such information in any of the following limited circumstances:
We have your consent.
We provide such information to trusted businesses or persons for the sole purpose of processing personally identifying information on our behalf. For example, for payment processing (credit card). These service providers have access to personal information that is required for their tasks.
When this is done, they are prohibited from using this information for other purposes and it is subject to agreements that oblige those parties to process such information only based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
We conclude that we are required by law or have a good faith belief that access, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of ConeXware, Inc., its users or the public.
In the event of a transfer of ownership of ConeXware, Inc., such as acquisition by or merger with another company, we will provide notice before any Personal Information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
ConexWare Inc. may be required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities.
In the context of an onward transfer, ConexWare Inc. has responsibility for the processing of personal information it receives under the Privacy Shield and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. The Privacy Shield organization shall remain liable under the Principles if its agent processes such personal information in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, unless the organization proves that it is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.
For more information on Privacy Shield Principles, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/EU-US-Framework.
Choice
You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to ConeXware, Inc. The notice we intend to provide where ConeXware, Inc. collects Personal Information on the Web should help you to make this choice. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you can still visit most of ConeXware, Inc.’s websites, but you will not be able to place an order or request support, as ConeXware, Inc. would need to contact you for support requests and order completion.
The PowerArchiver Release Newsletter is an opt-in e-mail newsletter to inform you when ConeXware, Inc. products have been updated. You will not be contacted for any marketing purposes beyond software update notices. If you wish to unsubscribe, you can do so by visiting the newsletters section.
Protecting Your Information
ConeXware, Inc. takes appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. Your data is encrypted with strict measures and access to your Personal Information is restricted to ConeXware, Inc. employees which may require access to the information in order to operate, develop or improve our services.
Updating Your Information
To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, ConeXware, Inc. wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. Where we collect Personal Information from you on the Web, our goal is to provide a means of contacting ConeXware, Inc. should you need to update or correct that Information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may contact us via e-mail with updates and corrections to your Personal Information.
If you wish to request access to, review or erase your Personal Information please contact us via e-mail.
Children’s Privacy
ConeXware, Inc.’s websites and products are not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age.
Commitment to Privacy
Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and ConeXware, Inc. is committed to meeting these demands. For more information about our practices regarding specific information or services that are not covered in this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
U.S.-EU Privacy Shield Framework
ConeXware, Inc. complies with the US-EU Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from Individual Customers in the European Union member countries. ConeXware, Inc. has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Privacy Principles of notice, choice, accountability for onward transfer, security, data integrity and purpose limitation, access, recourse, enforcement and liability. If there are any conflicts between the policies in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Privacy Principles, the Privacy Shield Privacy Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/
The Federal Trade Commission (FTC) has jurisdiction over ConeXware, Inc.’s compliance with the Privacy Shield.
All ConeXware, Inc. employees who handle Personal Data from Europe are required to comply with the Principles stated in this Policy.
In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, ConexWare Inc. commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact ConeXware Inc. at: privacy@conexware.com
ConexWare Inc, has further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to JAMS, an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States. ConeXware, Inc. will respond to any inquiries or complaints within forty-five (45) days. In the event that ConeXware, Inc. fails to respond or its response is insufficient or does not address the concern, please visit https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield/ for more information or to file a complaint. The services of JAMS are provided at no cost to you.
Please be informed that you have the possibility, under certain conditions, to invoke binding arbitration for complaints regarding Privacy Shield compliance not resolved by any of the other Privacy Shield mechanisms. For additional information, please visit:
https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=ANNEX-I-introduction
Contact Information
Questions, comments or complaints regarding the ConeXware, Inc.’s Privacy Policy, Privacy Shield, or data collection and processing practices can be mailed or emailed to:
ConeXware, Inc.
Latest News:
()
